Travelogue lecture photographs
Marist Archives and Special Collections
Travelogue lecture photographs
2.1.2.11.1
Marist College
MMM
MMM
MMM
  Box 1442
- Travelogue lecture photographs, 2.1.2.11.1
  - “Erik and Bunny are gonna get married!” (start show), circa 1924; 20; 3x4 color (Box 1442)
  - Camel caravan (start show), circa 1924; 21; 3x4 color (Box 1442)
  - Jasmine Tower with Taj Mahal in the distance (start show), circa 1924; 22; 8-204; 3x4 color (Box 1442)
  - Taj Mahal (start show), circa 1924; 23; 3x4 color (Box 1442)
  - Members of World Flight crew pushing the New Orleans airplane (start show), circa 1924; 24; 3x4 color (Box 1442)
  - Sail powered land vehicle (start show), circa 1924; 25; 3x4 color (Box 1442)
  - View of mountain from airplane (aerial view) (start show), circa 1924; 26; 3x4 b&w (Box 1442)
  - Man in rear seat on airplane (between reels 1 and 2), circa 1924; 27; 3x4 color (Box 1442)
  - Member of World Flight crew, posing for photograph (between reels 1 and 2), circa 1924; 28; 3x4 color (Box 1442)
  - Two members of World Flight crew in front of plane, one man holding raccoon (between reels 1 and 2), circa 1924; 29; 3x4 color (Box 1442)
  - Asian woman holding baby (between reels 1 and 2), circa 1924; 30; 3x4 color (Box 1442)
  - Grandmother (between reels 1 and 2), circa 1924; 31; 6-759; 3x4 color (Box 1442)
  - Two members of World Flight crew holding monkeys wearing pilot uniforms (between reels 1 and 2), circa 1924; 32; 3x4 color (Box 1442)
  - Three planes flying over golden temple (between reels 1 and 2), circa 1924; 33; 3x4 color (Box 1442)
  - Three planes flying over ship (between reels 1 and 2), circa 1924; 34; 3x4 color (Box 1442)
  - Fat Chinese shopkeeper (between reels 1 and 2), circa 1924; 35; 6-781; 3x4 color (Box 1442)
  - Two boats with one sail, side view (between reels 1 and 2), circa 1924; 36; 7-535; 3x4 color (Box 1442)
  Box 1443
- Travelogue lecture photographs, 2.1.2.11.1
  - Small junk with pointed sail and sampan under sail following behind (between reels 1 and 2), circa 1924; 1; 6-701; 3x4 color (Box 1443)
  - River in Malacca, one sail boat, one row boat (between reels 1 and 2), circa 1924; 2; 6-866; 3x4 color (Box 1443)
  - Seaplane on water, sunset (between reels 1 and 2), circa 1924; 3; 3x4 color (Box 1443)
  - Large white temple, Burma (between reels 1 and 2), circa 1924; 4; 3x4 color (Box 1443)
  - Man standing on sidewalk near temple (between reels 1 and 2), circa 1924; 5; 3x4 color (Box 1443)
  - Chinese temple with garden in Penang (between reels 1 and 2), circa 1924; 6; 6-832; 3x4 color (Box 1443)
  - Seaplane on water, snow covered hills in background (between reels 2 and 3), circa 1924; 7; 3x4 color (Box 1443)
  - Seaplane on water, snow covered hills and building in background, circa 1924; 8; 3x4 color (Box 1443)
  - View of town and water from airplane (aerial view) (between reels 2 and 3), circa 1924; 9; 3x4 color (Box 1443)
  - Four planes flying over railroad tracks beside water, mountains in distance (between reels 2 and 3), circa 1924; 10; 3x4 color (Box 1443)
  - Seaplane docked at port with boats (between reels 2 and 3), circa 1924; 11; 3x4 color (Box 1443)
  - View of sunset over mountains from airplane (aerial view) (between reels 2 and 3), circa 1924; 12; 3x4 color (Box 1443)
  - View of mountains in distance from airplane (aerial view) (between reels 2 and 3), circa 1924; 13; 3x4 color (Box 1443)
  - Rock path leading to buildings at base of mountain (between reels 2 and 3), circa 1924; 14; 3x4 color (Box 1443)
  - View of unidentified city from airplane (aerial view) (between reels 3 and 4), circa 1924; 15; 3x4 color (Box 1443)
  - View of Arc de Triomphe from airplane (aerial view), Paris, France (between reels 3 and 4), circa 1924; 16; 3x4 color (Box 1443)
  - View of Notre Dame Cathedral from airplane (aerial view), Paris, France (between reels 3 and 4), circa 1924; 17; 3x4 color (Box 1443)
  - View of unidentified city from airplane (aerial view) (between reels 3 and 4), circa 1924; 18; 3x4 color (Box 1443)
  - Six members of World Flight crew standing with man in civilian clothes (between reels 3 and 4), circa 1924; 19; 3x4 color (Box 1443)
  - German[?] cartoon (between reels 3 and 4), circa 1924; 20; 3x4 color (Box 1443)
  - Many men with cameras (between reels 4 and 5), circa 1924; 21; 3x4 color (Box 1443)
  - Three biplanes in flight (between reels 5 and 6), circa 1924; 22; 3x4 color (Box 1443)
  - View of Washington Monument, Reflection Pool and Lincoln Memorial from airplane (aerial view), Washington, D. C. (between reels 5 and 6), circa 1924; 23; 3x4 color (Box 1443)
  - Many planes flying over New York City, New York[?], circa 1924; 24; 3x4 color (Box 1443)
  - Lowell Thomas in front of airplane with members of World Flight crew, posing for photograph (between reels 5 and 6), circa 1924; 25; 3x4 color (Box 1443)
  - View of Capitol Building from airplane (aerial view), Washington, D. C. (between reels 5 and 6), circa 1924; 26; 3x4 color (Box 1443)
  - Fat Chinese shopkeeper (between reels 6 and 7), circa 1924; 27; 6-781; 3x4 color (Box 1443)
  - Seaplane on water, iceberg in background (between reels 6 and 7), circa 1924; 28; 3x4 color (Box 1443)
  - Men, women, and children in three row boats (between reels 6 and 7), circa 1924; 29; 3x4 color (Box 1443)
  - Two seaplanes, ship on water, icebergs in background (between reels 6 and 7), circa 1924; 30; 3x4 color (Box 1443)
  - Men in kayaks beside iceberg (between reels 6 and 7), circa 1924; 31; 3x4 color (Box 1443)
  - Two children on mound of snow (between reels 6 and 7), circa 1924; 32; 3x4 color (Box 1443)
  - World Flight crew member with children on lap (between reels 6 and 7), circa 1924; 33; 3x4 color (Box 1443)
  - World Flight crew member surrounded by children (between reels 6 and 7), circa 1924; 34; 3x4 color (Box 1443)
  - Marble Buddha in gold frame beside window (between reels 6 and 7), circa 1924; 35; 7-415; 3x4 color (Box 1443)
  - Canoe on kayak (between reels 6 and 7), circa 1924; 36; 3x4 color (Box 1443)
  Box 1444
- Travelogue lecture photographs, 2.1.2.11.1
  - Man in kayak (between reels 6 and 7), circa 1924; 1; 3x4 color (Box 1444)
  - Upside-down kayak (between reels 6 and 7), circa 1924; 2; 3x4 color (Box 1444)
  - Man in kayak as it rolls over (between reels 6 and 7), circa 1924; 3; 3x4 color (Box 1444)
  - View of sunset over water from airplane (aerial view) (between reels 6 and 7), circa 1924; 4; 3x4 color (Box 1444)
  - Clouds and sky, photograph taken from airplane (at end of reel 7), circa 1924; 5; 3x4 color (Box 1444)
  - View of sunset over mountains from airplane (aerial view) (at end of reel 7), circa 1924; 6; 3x4 color (Box 1444)
  - Man with camera looking at grounded airplane (at end of reel 7), circa 1924; 7; 3x4 color (Box 1444)
  - Man laying in bunk bed, looking at camera, circa 1924; 8; 3x4 color (Box 1444)